Total Experience: 9 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Electrical]

Notice Period: 2 Months

# Sridharrajan K (1) Featured

Senior Engineer seeking roles in Software Engineering, Full Stack Development, Software Development, Project Management, Angular, .Net core, SQL server, Azure Development



Current Designation: Senior Full Stack Engineer

Current Company: Cognizant Technology Solutions India Ltd

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Angular, .Net core, SQL server, Azure

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

## Summary

A lead Full Stack Engineer with 9 years of string experience in front-end development, back-end development areas with knowledge in SOA and Microservice architectures and with aspiration to masters in DevOps & Cloud. GOF patterns and OOP practitioner.

## Work Experience

#### Cognizant Technology Solutions India Ltd as Senior Full Stack Engineer Mar 2014 to Till Date

Expertise in web development using Angular 7+, .Net core, EF core, SQL server, Azure

Coding, Compiling, Unit Testing, integration, packaging and deployment of developed software

Work on POCs and cutting-edge features before they are integrated into the product

Managing the team (size of 15)

Good knowledge in project management

Provide progress reports to management and other affected stakeholders

Providing estimates and refining it as part of agile/waterfall project

Participate in architectural sessions and provide solutions to complex problems

Execute software development for outline work, support, maintain and document software functionality, design and architecture

Responsible for people management, including goal setting and providing performance feedback

TATA CMC as Dot Net Developer Aug 2013 to Feb 2014

AAAR Inc ( Development for Aclaratech U.S.A ) as Dot net Developer Nov 2011 to Jul 2013

#### **Education**

#### UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electrical) from Rajalakshmi Engineering College, Chennai in 2011

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Full Stack Engineer

Microsoft Azure Developer Associate

## **IT Skills**

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
C#.NET			9 Year(s)	
Asp.net mvc, Window Services, WCF			4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
Angular	9	2020	2 Year(s) 8 Month(s)	
.net core api	3.1	2020	2 Year(s)	
Azure Development			1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
SQL Server	2016	2020	7 Year(s)	
Jenkins, Ansible, TFS, SVN, GIT				
HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Docker				
EF core		2020	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
WCF SERVICES		2019	4 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
MicroServices		2020	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	
IT Project Management		2021	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)	

## **Languages Known**

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
ENGLISH	Expert			
TAMIL	Expert			

## **Affirmative Action**

Category: OBC - Creamy

Physically Challenged: No

## **Work Authorization**

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time